nutritionandhealing.com 2017-09-15

# Privacy Policy and Anti-Spam Statement - Nutrition and Healing

We at **Nutrition & Healing** take your privacy very seriously!

**e-Mail Address**  
When you subscribe to Nutrition & Healing’s eTips via e-mail, your e-mail address is placed in a database and used to send your e-letter issues. We will not sell, rent, or otherwise share your e-mail address with anyone. You can remove your address from our e-mailing list by following the instructions at the end of every e-mail we send.

Any e-mail you send to Nutrition & Healing is considered confidential unless you tell us otherwise. We will not add your name to our e-mail list without your permission. If your inquiry is about an order or subscription, our customer service staff will ask you to verify your identity by confirming information already in your record.

**Spam**  
If you believe that Nutrition & Healing has sent you unsolicited commercial e-mail (spam), please [contact us using this form](http://www.newmarkethealth.com/nahcontact/nah_contact_form.htm).

**Personal Information**  
We will never ask you for personal information–your credit card number, for example–except when you place an order. At that time, we will provide a secure (SSL, encrypted) connection and require you to submit only the information needed to complete and fulfill your order. Only authorized employees of NewMarket Health (our parent company) will have access to this information. NewMarket Health will not sell or rent this information to anyone, nor share it in any other way, unless required to by a law enforcement agency that takes the proper steps to require it. Please note that “personal information” does not include your mailing address (see Mailing Address below).

**Mailing Address**  
When you give us your mailing address, NewMarket Health will use this information to fulfill your order or subscription and to send you information on other products that may suit your interests. If you don’t want NewMarket Health to send you this other information, please contact our customer service department:  
Nutrition & Healing  
Attn: Customer Service  
702 Cathedral Street  
Baltimore, MD 21201

**Cookies**  
Cookies are small files placed on your computer by a web page when you visit it. They can be used to store all sorts of useful information to make your next visit easier and more convenient, but some people are uncomfortable not knowing what information is in a cookie. The Nutrition & Healing web site uses cookies only to compile statistics on the use of the various pages on our site (how many people visit each page and that sort of thing). We do not store or collect any personally identifiable information.

**We have a strict anti-spam policy!** We know how important your privacy is to you so we guarantee that we will NEVER sell your e-mail address. Please also note…you can remove yourself from our list at any time. We supply a link at the bottom of each e-mail to manage your subscription to the Health e-Tips e-letter. We also provide you with a mailing address, phone number and e-mail address to contact us if you have any problems.

We have implemented Google Analytics features based on Display Advertising (Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting). You can [opt-out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings. In addition, you can use the [Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) to disable tracking by Google Analytics. We will use the data provided by Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting to develop the site and content around our users’ interests.

**Policy against advertising our website using unsolicited email messages**  
We require that all e-mails promoting nutritionandhealing.com or its products are sent only to clients who have agreed to receive such messages. We prohibit any advertising of our brand and Web site using unsolicited email messages. Not complying with this policy will cause partnership termination and/or affiliate account termination. If you feel you’ve been sent unsolicited emails promoting our brand or website and would like to register a complaint, please email our abuse department (abuse@nutritionandhealing.com). We will immediately investigate all allegations made related to unsolicited messages.

For any other questions or concerns, please call us at 800-494-5726 (outside of the US, call 443-353-4162), or [contact us using this form](http://www.newmarkethealth.com/nahcontact/nah_contact_form.htm).
